Guide to the Planned Community Archives collection, 1960-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 9: Media 1960-2004
  - Subseries 2: Slides, 1960-1990
    - Single Family Detached, 1970s (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - Slide: Exterior view of residential construction, lake in background, August 1980; 1.
      - Slide: Exterior view of residential construction, lake in background, August 1980; 2.
      - Slide: View of lake from inside residential construction, August 1980; 3.
      - Slide: Sterling Series home designs, by Trafalgar House, finished models, August 1980; 4.
      - Slide: Sterling Series home designs, by Trafalgar House, exterior views, August 1980; 5.
    - Swimming Pools, Norths Hills and Kites, 1970s (Box 126, Folder 1)
      563
    - Reston, 1980s (Box 127, Folder 1)
      564
      - Slide: Men with architectural model of Reston Town Center, ca. 1988; 1.
      - Slide: Men with architectural model of Reston Town Center, ca. 1988; 2.
      - Slide: Viewings of architectural model of Reston Town Center, ca. 1988; 3.
      - Slide: Pumpkin patch and red wagons in foreground, 1988; 4.
      - Slide: Community festival in Washington Plaza, 1988; 5.
      - Slide: Community festival in Washington Plaza, 1988; 6.
      - Slide: Community parade, 1960s theme, 1988; 7.
      - Slide: Community festival reaching the banks of Washington Plaza, 1988; 8.
    - Reston, 1980s-1990s (Box 128, Folder 1)
      565
      - Slide: Children ice skating on rink in Reston Town Center, February 1991; 1.
      - Slide: Residents enjoying completed area of Reston Town Center, 1991; 2.
      - Slide: Parents and children ice skating on rink in Reston Town Center, February 1991; 3.
      - Slide: Street view of Reston Town Center, 1991; 4.
      - Slide: Construction zone with truck, ca. 1987; 5.
      - Slide: Construction zone with truck, 1987; 6.
      - Slide: Aerial view of Lake Anne, ca. 1987; 7.
      - Slide: Aerial view of Reston's communities, 1987; 8.
      - Slide: Aerial view of Reston, with the International Center in background, 1987; 9.
      - Slide: Aerial view of Lake Anne in autumn, 1987; 10.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Patrick Kane", August 1982; 11.
    - Dulles Toll Road, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 1)
      566
      - Dulles Toll Road, with Reston International Center in background, November 1984; 1.
      - Slide: James Douglass, "Reston Expressway (Dulles Toll Road), under construction", August 1984; 2.
    - Horses, 1970s (Box 130, Folder 1)
      567
    - Wooded Trails, 1970s (Box 130, Folder 2)
      - Slide: Robert Llewellyn, "Residents enjoying one of the wooded trails in Reston", October 1978; 1.
      - Slide: Robert Llewellyn, "Wooded Trail in Reston", October 1978; 2.
      - Slide: Robert Llewellyn, "A creek breaks up a wooded trail in Reston", October 1978; 3.
    - Old Reston Visitor Center, 1980s (Box 130, Folder 3)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Old Reston Visitor's Center, Interior decor", November 1982; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Old Reston Visitor's Center, Interior decor", November 1982; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Old Reston Visitor's Center, Interior decor", November 1982; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Old Reston Visitor's Center, Interior decor", November 1982; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Old Reston Visitor's Center, Interior decor", November 1982; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Old Reston Visitor's Center, Interior decor", November 1982; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Old Reston Visitor's Center, Interior decor", November 1982a; 7.
    - Bicentennial Airshow and Parade, 1976 (Box 131, Folder 1)
      568
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Kings Dominion and Firestone sponsored hot air balloon at bicentennial air show", 1976; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Residents gazing towards sky at bicentennial air show", 1976; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Kings Dominion and Firestone sponsored hot air balloon", 1976; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Park Ranger, Uncle Sam, and Kings Dominion/Firestone hot air balloon", 1976; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Uncle Same parachuting at the bicentennial air show", 1976; 5.
    - Top of Building Looking Down, 1984 (Box 132, Folder 1)
      569
    - Miscellaneous Buildings, 1985 (Box 132, Folder 2)
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "GTE Telenet Operations building", May 1985; 1.
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "ATandT Communications Consumer Market Sales Center, lobby", May 1985; 2.
    - Reston Community, 1985 (Box 133, Folder 1)
      570
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Cedar Cove homes", May 1986; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston International Center Sheraton Hotel courtyard", May 1986; 2.
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "Sailing on one of Reston's lakes", May 1985; 3.
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "Sailing on one of Reston's lakes", May 1985; 4.
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "Sailing Kayaker on one of Reston's lakes", May 1985; 5.
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "Fishing in Reston lake", May 1985; 6.
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "Small child flying a kite", May 1985; 7.
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "View of lakefront homes in autumn", May 1985; 8.
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "Couple in a canoe in one of Reston's lakes in autumn", May 1985; 9.
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "Sailing by Cedar Cove homes", May 1985; 10.
    - Exercise, 1985 (Box 134, Folder 1)
      571
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "Discus champion, 1985 Herndon High School", May 1985; 1.
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "Discus champion, 1985 Herndon High School", May 1985; 2.
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "Discus champion, 1985 Herndon High School", May 1985; 3.
    - Exercise with Trainer, 1985 (Box 134, Folder 2)
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "Exercising with personal trainer", May 1985; 1.
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "Exercising with personal trainer", May 1985; 2.
    - Sunset Aerial View, 1985 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Children's Sports, 1980s (Box 135, Folder 1)
      572
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston Rockets youth soccer game", June 1982; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston Rockets youth soccer game", June 1982; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston Rockets youth soccer game", June 1982; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston Rockets youth soccer game", June 1982; 4.
    - Advertisements, Art and Churches, 1970s (Box 136, Folder 1)
      573
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Golden Autumn program for Reston Fall Home Tour, color", ca. 1991; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "This is the Life" Reston printed advertisement, "One of the nicest things about Reston is the downtown," color, ca. 1991; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, 'This is the Life' Reston printed advertisement, 'In Reston, you don't have to move out to move up,' color, ca. 1991; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Covers of various magazines featuring Reston articles, color", June 1967; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "'This is the Life' Reston printed advertisement, tagline, color", ca. 1991; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Print advertisement for Reston, tagline, color", ca. 1991; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston print advertisement, 18 images, tagline, color", February 1985; 7.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston Expressway Builder's Breakfast, tagline, black and white", February 1985; 8.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston Expressway Builder's Breakfast, tagline, black and white", February 1985; 9.
      - Slide: Ander, "Interior of the Greater Reston Arts Center, patrons, color", ca. 1985; 10.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Costumed musicians at community festival", no date; 11.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Costumed musicians at community festival", no date; 12.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "One of Reston's houses of worship, exterior, NAME UNKNOWN", June 1982; 13.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "One of Reston's houses of worship, exterior, young family and minister, NAME UNKNOWN", December 1973; 14.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Interior view of one of Reston's houses of worship, NAME UNKNOWN", ca. 1980; 15.
    - Winter, 1982 (Box 137, Folder 1)
      574
      - Slide: Ander, "Snow covered Reston Information Center", February 1982; 1.
      - Slide: Ander, "Snow covered landscape of Reston, cranes in background", February 1982; 2.
      - Slide: Ander, "Snow covered landscape of Reston, townhouses in background, facing frontwards", February 1982; 3.
    - McDonalds/Pizza Hut, 1982 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - People Playing in the Snow, 1982 (Box 137, Folder 3)
      - Slide: Robert Llewellyn, "Children ice skating on frozen Lake Anne", February 1973; 1.
    - People by the Lake, 1982 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - People Walking by Building, 1982 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Mallards Landing, 1980s (Box 138, Folder 1)
      575
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Mallard's Landing lakeside homes, interior construction", August 1980; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Mallard's Landing lakeside homes, exterior construction", August 1980; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Mallard's Landing lakeside homes, completed model", August 1980; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Mallard's Landing town homes, completed models", April 1981; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakeside view of Mallard's Landing homes construction", August 1980; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakeside view of Mallard's Landing apartment construction", August 1980; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Mallard's Landing lakeside homes, interior construction", August 1980; 7.
    - Mediterranean Villa, 1980s (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Mediterranean Villa first addition architectural models", May 1969; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Mediterranean Villa first addition architectural models", May 1969; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Mediterranean Villa completed models", June 1971; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Mediterranean Villa and Wainwright Cluster architectural elevation, Route 606", May 1969; 4.
    - Moorings Cluster, 1980s (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "The Moorings Cluster architectural elevation", April 1971; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "The Moorings Cluster lakeside homes construction", May 1971; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "The Moorings Cluster town homes architectural elevation, sem-color", January 1970; 3.
    - Newbridge, 1970s (Box 138, Folder 4)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Newbridge Town homes, completed models", October 1974; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Newbridge Town homes, construction", ca. 1973; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Newbridge Town homes, early construction and surveyors", ca. 1973; 3.
    - Northgate Square, 1970s (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Northshore, 1970s (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Orchard Green, 1970s (Box 138, Folder 7)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Northshore Town homes, completed model", ca. 1972; 1.
    - Pinecrest, 1970s (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Regency Square, 1970s (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Reston Material, 1990s (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Bicentennial Air Show and Parade, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 1)
      576
    - Wethersfield, 1970s (Box 140, Folder 1)
      577
    - Wheelwright, 1970s (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Briddle Ridge/Polo Club, 1960s (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Single Family Detached, 1960s (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - People Working, 1970s (Box 141, Folder 1)
      578
    - Interiors of Residential and Commercial Buildings, 1970s (Box 142, Folder 1)
      579
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Early construction of single family homes on Lake Audubon", October 1979; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lake Audubon, with early phases of construction in background", October 1979; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lake Audubon, with early phases of construction in background", October 1979; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Fountain in the middle of Lake Anne", no date; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for multi-purpose room", April 1977; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for bathroom", April 1977; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for dining room", April 1977; 7.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for informal dining room", April 1977; 8.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for formal dining room", April 1977; 9.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for master bedroom", April 1977; 10.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for child's room", April 1977; 11.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for family's living room", April 1977; 12.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for the kitchen", April 1977; 13.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for family's living room", April 1977; 14.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for master bedroom", April 1977; 15.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for master bedroom", April 1977; 16.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for formal red living room", April 1977; 17.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for formal red living room", April 1977; 18.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for the kitchen", April 1977; 19.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for bathroom", April 1977; 20.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for elevated dining alcove", April 1977; 21.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for the kitchen", April 1977; 22.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for child's room", April 1977; 23.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for family recreation room", April 1977; 24.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Front exterior of model lakeside home", ca. 1978; 25.
      - Slide: Schnabel Photography, "Interior of model home and suggested design elements", no date; 26.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Back exterior of model lakeside home under construction", July 1978; 27.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Front exterior of model lakeside home", ca. 1978; 28.
    - Volleyball, Tennis, Soccer, Skating, Racquetball and Picnic Pavilion, 1970s-1980s (Box 143, Folder 1)
      580
    - Hunt Club Cluster, 1960s (Box 144, Folder 1)
      581
    - Hunter Green, 1970s (Box 144, Folder 2)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of Hunters Green cluster town homes during construction", ca. 1970; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Hunters Green cluster architectural elevation", July 1970; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Hunters Green town home architectural models", July 1970; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Hunters Green brick town homes, completed models", July 1972; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Hunters Green brick town homes during construction", November 1971; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Hunters Green town home architectural models", ca. 1970; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Hunters Green brick town homes during construction", November 1971; 7.
    - Hunter's Square, 1980s (Box 144, Folder 3)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Hunters Square town homes, completed models", April 1981; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Hunters Square town homes during construction", November 1980; 2.
    - Inlet Cluster, 1970s (Box 144, Folder 4)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Inlet Cluster town homes aerial view in autumn", October 1972; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Inlet Cluster town homes aerial view in autumn", ca. 1972; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Inlet Cluster town homes completed models", October 1971; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Inlet Cluster town homes architectural elevation", April 1971; 4.
    - Lakeside, 1960s (Box 144, Folder 5)
      - Slide: William Graham, "Lakeside Town homes, architectural elevation", April 1968; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakeside Town homes, view from across the lake", June 1969; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakeside Town homes, completed models", October 1969; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakeside Town homes, completed models", ca. 1969; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakeside Town homes under construction", January 1969; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakeside Town homes under construction", January 1969; 6.
    - Lakewinds, 1970s (Box 144, Folder 6)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakewinds Town homes architectural elevation", September 1976; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakewinds Town homes under construction", August 1980; 2.
    - Lakewood, 1970s (Box 144, Folder 7)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakewood Town homes under construction", October 1979; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakewood Town homes completed models", April 1981; 2.
    - Link Pond, 1970s (Box 144, Folder 8)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Link Pond Town homes completed models", ca. 1974; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Link Pond Town homes during construction", ca. 1974; 2.
    - Ivy Oak Condo, 1970s (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - People Working, 1980s (Box 145, Folder 1)
      582
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Technician working on computer", June 1966; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Core office workspace with busy employees", June 1966; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston scientist conducting experiments", June 1966; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston architect at drawing table", May 1968; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Employees gathered around specialized equipment", June 1968; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Looking over an architect's shoulder as they render Reston's home designs", ca. 1973; 6.
      - Slide: William A. Graham, "Reston architect with special design glasses in foreground", June 1968; 7.
    - People Working, 1970s (Box 146, Folder 1)
      583
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Three businessmen strolling in front of the Reston International Center", ca. 1972; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Father and young children in front of sculpture at Lake Anne Plaza", May 1971; 2.
    - Litton, 1970s (Box 147, Folder 1)
      584
      - Slide: Anonymous, "MOTOROLA, one of Reston's technological residents", ca. 1972; 1.
    - Mid-Atlantic Gift Center, 1970s (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Post Office, 1970s (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Schoenstedt, 1970s (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Scope, 1970s (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "SCOPE Industries completed building, employees entering main entrance", December 1966; 1.
      - Slide: J. Janson, "SCOPE Industries architectural scheme", ca. 1966; 2.
    - Sperry, 1970s (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of SPERRY building with rooftop snow", October 1980; 1.
    - Sunset Square, 1970s (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - US Geological Survey, 1970s (Box 147, Folder 8)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Close up of United States Geological Survey sign outside Reston facility", ca. 1974; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of USGS facility in Reston", October 1980; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "USGS Reston facility architectural elevation", ca. 1972; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "USGS Reston facility during construction", September 1972; 4.
    - Industrial, 1970s (Box 147, Folder 9)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of campus west and east footprints, architectural model", no date; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Office complex within Reston's industrial park", no date; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Architectural model for the commons water element", no date; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Construction zone in new Reston industrial park", no date; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Parkridge architectural elevation", no date; 5.
      - Slide: Lee Sammis, "Campus Commons architectural elevation", no date; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Exterior view of the TANDEM computers office facility in Reston", January 1983; 7.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Exterior view of DECA facility in Reston", October 1976; 8.
      - Slide: Ander, "Construction zone of new industrial park in Reston", February 1982; 9.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Basketball player in the shadow of Reston corporate buildings", no date; 10.
    - Swimming Pools, North Hills and Kites, 1980s (Box 148, Folder 1)
      585
    - Interiors of Residential and Commercial Buildings, 1980s-1990s (Box 149, Folder 1)
      586
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of Lake Anne Village Center", no date; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of Lake Anne", August 1980; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Community festival at Washington Plaza", May 1971; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston resident emerging from pedestrian underpass flanked with murals", no date; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for child's bedroom", March 1973; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Model home interior design suggestion for recreation room", March 1967; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Bloomingdale's decorated home giveaway, formal dining room", 1977; 7.
      - Slide: Lisanti, "Model home interior design suggestion for living room", 1984; 8.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Newspaper clippings and headlines regarding Reston's national significance", April 1967; 9.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "North Hills Park architectural elevation from inside display case", March 1992; 10.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "The State of the Arts in Reston report", October 1993; 11.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Golden Autumn Tour of Reston marketing package", January 1992; 12.
      - Slide: Helen Horsley, "Reston Arts Home Tour t-shirt design", ca. 1992; 13.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "'Live in the Land of Opportunity' Reston advertisement, 7 images, tagline, color", August 1990; 14.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Corporate logos of Reston's industrial park residents, tagline, color", August 1990; 15.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "'Reston understands that the power lunch should also satisfy your appetite' Reston ad campaign, 16 images, black and white", May 1990; 16.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "'Reston understands that the business lunch should also satisfy your appetite' Reston ad campaign, 9 images, color", August 1990; 17.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston Land Corporation Tuesday Movie Matinee promotional poster, color", no date; 18.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Five different Reston advertisements, 3 color, 2 black and white all sail boats on the water", no date; 19.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Broadlands 'We've Got Six Reasons to Celebrate' color advertisement, color", no date; 20.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston Land Corporation advertisement", February 1990; 21.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "'In Northern Virginia, the best place to work is also the best place not to work' Reston advertisement, 7 images, black and white", May 1990; 22.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston Town Center architectural elevation", May 1990; 23.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lake Port town homes design styles and information, advertisement, color", March 1989; 24.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Beacon Hill homes design styles and information, advertisement, color", March 1989; 25.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Hemingway Wrenn Town homes design styles and information, elevation, color", March 1989; 26.
    - Reston, 1980s (Box 150, Folder 1)
      587
    - Baldwin Grove Condo, 1990s (Box 151, Folder 1)
      588
      - Slide: Narod and Pruett Photographers, "Baldwin Grove Condominiums completed model, front exterior color", ca. 1993; 1.
      - Slide: Narod and Pruett Photographers, "Baldwin Grove Condominiums completed model, front exterior color", February 1993; 2.
      - Slide: Narod and Pruett Photographers, "Baldwin Grove Condominium architectural elevation, front exterior, color", March 1992; 3.
    - Bentana Park Condo, 1970s (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Cedar Ridge Apartments, 1960s (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Cedar Ridge Apartments architectural elevation", May 1969; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Cedar Ridge Apartments completed models, front exterior, color", October 1969; 2.
    - Charter Oak Apartments, 1970s (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Chestnut Grove Apartments, 1970s (Box 151, Folder 5)